spicylingerie.com 2015-06-23

# Privacy Policy,

SpicyLingerie.com Privacy Policy :

This privacy statement is created to show our commitment to your privacy.

This site uses cookies to maintain shopping cart information and to monitor the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

This site uses an online shopping cart order form that collects contact information (name, address, email address, credit card information) with the purpose of processing and shipping orders.

This site collects IP addresses for the purpose of tracking an user's session. This information gives us information on which areas and products are visited. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that an user session will be tracked, and WE KNOW WHERE YOU ARE. This information provide to police investigation the credit card fraudulent only.

We do not sell or market email addresses, credit card information, and any personal information of our visitors and customers to other companies.

Warning: To Those That Might Attempt Credit Card Fraud

Credit card fraud can not and will not be tolerated. It undermines the entire growth of the Internet and computer companies worldwide. We actively and aggressively fight all forms of credit card fraud.

WHAT CONSTITUTES CREDIT CARD FRAUD? Credit card fraud has been committed if you attempt to use someone else's credit card without their approval or if you use your credit card and then claim that you did not authorize the transaction.

NOTICE: We report all fraudulent orders and unauthorized credit card activity to the US Postal Inspectors, Local Police Department, FBI and the National White Collar Crime Center (NW3C).

WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU COMMIT CREDIT CARD FRAUD? You will be reported to the FBI and you will be sued by us. This may result in an action against you for the amount disputed, plus the cost of paying the collection agency and/or lawyers processed by an international collection agency with independent representatives in America, Europe and Asia, plus costs for round trip airfare, motel, food, and labor costs for our own designated agent to appear in court. Credit card fraud is a serious offense and will be prosecuted to the fullest extent possible. Our no tolerance policy of fighting back each and every case of credit card fraud will cost you much more money than the original amount you received.

HOW DO WE PROVE YOUR IDENTITY? Your identity is available through your Internet Service Provider (including AOL and dynamic IP's).

HOW DO WE COLLECT? We may file liens on your property, bank account, and/or garnish your wages. This may also result in a report being filed with 3 major credit reporting agencies once our case is won.

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!,[click here](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html).   
SpicyLingerie.com Privacy Policy :

This privacy statement is created to show our commitment to your privacy.

This site uses cookies to maintain shopping cart information and to monitor the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

This site uses an online shopping cart order form that collects contact information (name, address, email address, credit card information) with the purpose of processing and shipping orders.

This site collects IP addresses for the purpose of tracking an user's session. This information gives us information on which areas and products are visited. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that an user session will be tracked, and WE KNOW WHERE YOU ARE. This information provide to police investigation the credit card fraudulent only.

We do not sell or market email addresses, credit card information, and any personal information of our visitors and customers to other companies.

Warning: To Those That Might Attempt Credit Card Fraud

Credit card fraud can not and will not be tolerated. It undermines the entire growth of the Internet and computer companies worldwide. We actively and aggressively fight all forms of credit card fraud.

WHAT CONSTITUTES CREDIT CARD FRAUD? Credit card fraud has been committed if you attempt to use someone else's credit card without their approval or if you use your credit card and then claim that you did not authorize the transaction.

NOTICE: We report all fraudulent orders and unauthorized credit card activity to the US Postal Inspectors, Local Police Department, FBI and the National White Collar Crime Center (NW3C).

WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU COMMIT CREDIT CARD FRAUD? You will be reported to the FBI and you will be sued by us. This may result in an action against you for the amount disputed, plus the cost of paying the collection agency and/or lawyers processed by an international collection agency with independent representatives in America, Europe and Asia, plus costs for round trip airfare, motel, food, and labor costs for our own designated agent to appear in court. Credit card fraud is a serious offense and will be prosecuted to the fullest extent possible. Our no tolerance policy of fighting back each and every case of credit card fraud will cost you much more money than the original amount you received.

HOW DO WE PROVE YOUR IDENTITY? Your identity is available through your Internet Service Provider (including AOL and dynamic IP's).

HOW DO WE COLLECT? We may file liens on your property, bank account, and/or garnish your wages. This may also result in a report being filed with 3 major credit reporting agencies once our case is won.

_
